Guide to the Deceased Alumni files, 1868-1990.
Deceased Alumni files, 1868-1990.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Deceased Alumni files, 1868-1990.
41-2-877
Cornell University.Public Affairs Records.
424 cubic ft.
Correspondence, photographs, clippings, and biographical data.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Correspondence, photographs, clippings, and biographical data concerning Cornell University alumni.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, photographs, clippings, and biographical data concerning Cornell University alumni.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
To place a request, ask for staff assistance. Provide alumnus's/alumna's name, and death date if known.
The dates listed in the container list below are the alumni's/alumnae's death dates. The date is sometimes the date the file was pulled and may not correspond exactly to the date of death. For staff, retrieving box numbers from the alumni database is advised, or checking adjacent years if a folder is not found.
There is no Box 148.
Access Restrictions:
Living alumni files are stored separately. Only records of deceased alumni are open for research.
RELATED MATERIALS
For alumni killed during World War Two see World War II servicemen alumni files, 1939-1945, #41-2-822.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Arranged alphabetically within groups.
Deceased Before 1963
Boxes1-147
Deceased From 1963 Onward
Boxes 148-348
Deceased From July 1985 Onward
Boxes 349-
CONTAINER LIST
- Deceased Before 1963
  - Abra-Aldr (Box 1)
  - Aldr-Ande (Box 2)
  - Ande-Atki (Box 3)
  - Atki-Baco (Box 4)
  - Baco-Ball (Box 5)
  - Ball-Barr (Box 6)
  - Barr-Bead (Box 7)
  - Bead-Bell (Box 8)
  - Bell-Bern (Box 9)
  - Bern-Birt (Box 10)
  - Birt-Bloo (Box 11)
  - Bloo-Boot (Box 12)
  - Boot-Brad (Box 13)
  - Brad-Brig (Box 14)
  - Brig-Brow (Box 15)
  - Brow-Brue (Box 16)
  - Brug-Burd (Box 17)
  - Burd-Butl (Box 18)
  - Butl-Cana (Box 19)
  - Cana-Carr (Box 20)
  - Carr-Cham (Box 21)
  - Cham-Chol (Box 22)
  - Chol-Clar (Box 23)
  - Clar-Coha (Box 24)
  - Cohe-Con (Box 25)
  - Con-Coo (Box 26)
  - Coo-Cow (Box 27)
  - Cow-Cron (Box 28)
  - Cron-Curr (Box 29)
  - Curr-Dann (Box 30)
  - Dans-Davi (Box 31)
  - Davi-Del (Box 32)
  - Del-Dic (Box 33)
  - Dic-Dona (Box 34)
  - Dona-Dri (Box 35)
  - Dro-Dutc (Box 36)
  - Dutc-Edso (Box 37)
  - Edwa-Elli (Box 38)
  - Elli-Etle (Box 39)
  - Etle-Farr (Box 40)
  - Farr-Ferr (Box 41)
  - Ferr-Fish (Box 42)
  - Fish-Fols (Box 43)
  - Folw-Fowl (Box 44)
  - Fox-Frie (Box 45)
  - Frie-Gain (Box 46)
  - Gais-Gast (Box 47)
  - Gate-Giff (Box 48)
  - Gign-Godd (Box 49)
  - Godd-Good (Box 50)
  - Good-Grey (Box 51)
  - Gray-Grif (Box 52)
  - Grig-Hack (Box 53)
  - Hack-Halp (Box 54)
  - Hals-Hard (Box 55)
  - Hard-Hart (Box 56)
  - Hart-Hayd (Box 57)
  - Hayd-Helf (Box 58)
  - Helle-Herr (Box 59)
  - Herr-Hill (Box 60)
  - Hill-Hoff (Box 61)
  - Hoof-Hoos (Box 62)
  - Hoov-Howa (Box 63)
  - Howa-Huds (Box 64)
  - Hue-Hurl (Box 65)
  - Hurs-Ivan (Box 66)
  - Ives-Jenk (Box 67)
  - Jenk-John (Box 68)
  - John-Joyn (Box 69)
  - Judd-Kell (Box 70)
  - Kell-Kerl (Box 71)
  - Kern-Kins (Box 72)
  - Kins-Knoe (Box 73)
  - Knop-Kuhn (Box 74)
  - Kuhn-Lang (Box 75)
  - Lang-Laws (Box 76)
  - Lawt-Lest (Box 77)
  - Leuc-Lind (Box 78)
  - Lind-Lorb (Box 79)
  - Lord-Lyle (Box 80)
  - Lyma-McCl (Box 81)
  - McCl-McDo (Box 82)
  - MacD-McKa (Box 83)
  - McKa-McNe (Box 84)
  - McNe-Mann (Box 85)
  - Marv-Mayn (Box 86)
  - Marv-Mayn (Box 87)
  - Mayn-Merr (Box 88)
  - Merr-Mill (Box 89)
  - Mill-Mitc (Box 90)
  - Mitr-Moor (Box 91)
  - More-Mosh (Box 92)
  - Mosk-Murp (Box 93)
  - Murr-Nett (Box 94)
  - Nett-Nola (Box 95)
  - Nolk-O'Co (Box 96)
  - O'Dan-Osbu (Box 97)
  - Oseg-Pain (Box 98)
  - Pain-Pars (Box 99)
  - Part-Pend (Box 100)
  - Pend-Phel (Box 101)
  - Phil-Plau (Box 102)
  - Plea-Powe (Box 103)
  - Powe-Purd (Box 104)
  - Purd-Rath (Box 105)
  - Rath-Reil (Box 106)
  - Reim-Rich (Box 107)
  - Rich-Robe (Box 108)
  - Robe-Roge (Box 109)
  - Roge-Ross (Box 110)
  - Ross-Ruyt (Box 111)
  - Ryan-Saul (Box 112)
  - Saun-Schm (Box 113)
  - Schm-Scof (Box 114)
  - Scoo-Serl (Box 115)
  - Serr-Shea (Box 116)
  - Shea-Shin (Box 117)
  - Shin-Simp (Box 118)
  - Sirm-Smit (Box 119)
  - Smith-Smith (Box 120)
  - Smit-Snyd (Box 121)
  - Sobe-Spra (Box 122)
  - Spra-Stee (Box 123)
  - Stee-Stig (Box 124)
  - Stil-Stra (Box 125)
  - Stra-Suor (Box 126)
  - Supe-Tapp (Box 127)
  - Tapp-Tenn (Box 128)
  - Tenn-Thom (Box 129)
  - Thom-Thom (Box 130)
  - Tomp-Trem (Box 131)
  - Tren-turn (Box 132)
  - Turo-VanB (Box 133)
  - VanB-Vava (Box 134)
  - Veat-Waig (Box 135)
  - Wain-Wann (Box 136)
  - Ward-Watk (Box 137)
  - Watr-Weih (Box 138)
  - Weil-Wess (Box 139)
  - West-Whel (Box 140)
  - Whel-Whit (Box 141)
  - Whit-Wilk (Box 142)
  - Will-Will (Box 143)
  - Will-Wins (Box 144)
  - Wint-Wood (Box 145)
  - Wood-Wyve (Box 146)
  - Yager-Zusk (Box 147)
  - No Box 148 (Box 148)
- Deceased From 1963 Onward
  - A-Berm, 1963-1966 (Box 149)
  - Berr-Carr, 1963-1966 (Box 150)
  - Carp-Davido, 1963-1966 (Box 151)
  - Davids-Fe, 1963-1966 (Box 152)
  - Fi-Gram, 1963-1966 (Box 153)
  - Gram-Hodg, 1963-1966 (Box 154)
  - Hodh-Ken, 1963-1966 (Box 155)
  - Keo-L, 1963-1966 (Box 156)
  - M-Morr, 1963-1966 (Box 157)
  - Mors-Pfl, 1963-1966 (Box 158)
  - Ph-Rube, 1963-1966 (Box 159)
  - Rubf-Stei, 1963-1966 (Box 160)
  - Stej-Wak, 1963-1966 (Box 161)
  - Wal-Z, 1963-1966 (Box 162)
  - A-Del, 1966 (Box 163)
  - Det-Hol, 1966 (Box 164)
  - Hoov-Murr, 1966 (Box 165)
  - N-Spec, 1966 (Box 166)
  - Sped-Z, 1966 (Box 167)
  - A-Bol, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 168)
  - Bon-Col, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 169)
  - Com-D, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 170)
  - E-Ga, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 171)
  - Ge-He, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 172)
  - Hi-Kel, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 173)
  - Ken-Mars, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 174)
  - Mart-Mose, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 175)
  - Moss-Pre, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 176)
  - Pri-Sc, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 177)
  - Se-Ta, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 178)
  - Te-Wile, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 179)
  - Will-Z, January 1967-May 1967 (Box 180)
  - A-Crowe, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 181)
  - Crowl-Hare, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 182)
  - Harr-Mac, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 183)
  - Mad-Sed, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 184)
  - See-Z, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 185)
  - A-Bir, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 186)
  - Bis-Cof, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 187)
  - Cog-Dud, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 188)
  - Duf-Gile, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 189)
  - Gill-Horn, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 190)
  - Hors-Lande, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 191)
  - Landi-McK, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 192)
  - Mcl-Patte, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 193)
  - Patto-Rog, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 194)
  - Roi-Spi, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 195)
  - Spo-Vang, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 196)
  - Vanh-Z, June 1967-July 1968 (Box 197)
  - A-Bo, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 198)
  - Br-Cov, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 199)
  - Cox-Elle, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 200)
  - Elli-Gre, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 201)
  - Gri-Ing, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 202)
  - Inm-La, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 203)
  - Le-Metc, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 204)
  - Matz-Per, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 205)
  - Pet-Sanb, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 206)
  - Sand-Sw, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 207)
  - Sy-Wol, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 208)
  - Woo-Z, July 1969-July 1970 (Box 209)
  - A-Bli, July 1970-July 1971 (Box 210)
  - Blo-Clar, July 1970-July 1971 (Box 211)
  - Claw-Dori, July 1970-July 1971 (Box 212)
  - Dorr-Geh, July 1970-July 1971 (Box 213)
  - Gei-Heb, July 1970-July 1971 (Box 214)
  - Her-King, July 1970-July 1971 (Box 215)
  - Kings-Mar, July 1970-July 1971 (Box 216)
  - Mas-Os, July 1970-July 1971 (Box 217)
  - Ot-Rub, July 1970-July 1971 (Box 218)
  - Ruc-Sto, July 1970-July 1971 (Box 219)
  - Srt-Z, July 1970-July 1971 (Box 220)
  - A-Boug, July 1971-July 1972 (Box 221)
  - Bour-Cross, July 1971-July 1972 (Box 222)
  - Crossa-Foo, July 1971-July 1972 (Box 223)
  - For-Hartn, July 1971-July 1972 (Box 224)
  - Hartw-Joh, July 1971-July 1972 (Box 225)
  - Jon-Li, July 1971-July 1972 (Box 226)
  - Lo-Munn, July 1971-July 1972 (Box 227)
  - Munr-Q, July 1971-July 1972 (Box 228)
  - R-Sim, July 1971-July 1972 (Box 229)
  - Sis-Wate, July 1971-July 1972 (Box 230)
  - Watk-Z, July 1971-July 1972 (Box 231)
  - A-B, July 1972-July 1973 (Box 232)
  - Call-Dext, July 1972-July 1973 (Box 233)
  - Dick-Ger, July 1972-July 1973 (Box 234)
  - Gian-Hub, July 1972-July 1973 (Box 235)
  - Hud-Lein, July 1972-July 1973 (Box 236)
  - Lenz-Mille, July 1972-July 1973 (Box 237)
  - Milli-Park, July 1972-July 1973 (Box 238)
  - Parr-Roi, July 1972-July 1973 (Box 239)
  - Rom-Stanl, July 1972-July 1973 (Box 240)
  - Stant-Wall, July 1972-July 1973 (Box 241)
  - Wals-Z, July 1972-July 1973 (Box 242)
  - A-Bran, July 1973-July 1974 (Box 243)
  - Brau-Da, July 1973-July 1974 (Box 244)
  - De-Gillies, July 1973-July 1974 (Box 245)
  - Gillig-I, July 1973-July 1974 (Box 246)
  - J-L, July 1973-July 1974 (Box 247)
  - M-N, July 1973-July 1974 (Box 248)
  - O-Ross, July 1973-July 1974 (Box 249)
  - Rot-Thomas, July 1973-July 1974 (Box 250)
  - Thomson-Z, July 1973-July 1974 (Box 251)
  - Abb-Buff, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 252)
  - Bun-Dor, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 253)
  - Dos-Haa, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 254)
  - Hai-Jon, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 255)
  - Jor-May, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 256)
  - Mc-Per, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 257)
  - Pet-Sch, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 258)
  - Sco-Trim, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 259)
  - Trip-Z, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 260)
  - Abb-Bro, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 261)
  - Bru-Col, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 262)
  - Colt-David, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 263)
  - Davie-Fil, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 264)
  - Fin-Guy, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 265)
  - Ha-Hsia, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 266)
  - Hsii-Kreid, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 267)
  - Krein-Mass, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 268)
  - Mat-Nor, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 269)
  - Ob-Rob, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 270)
  - Roc-Sp, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 271)
  - St-Wear, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 272)
  - Weav-Z, July 1974-July 1976 (Box 273)
  - A-Cl, July 1976-July 1977 (Box 274)
  - Cl-E, July 1976-July 1977 (Box 275)
  - F-He, July 1976-July 1977 (Box 276)
  - Hi-Kim, July 1976-July 1977 (Box 277)
  - Kin-Mit, July 1976-July 1977 (Box 278)
  - Mo-Phil, July 1976-July 1977 (Box 279)
  - Phip-Sch, July 1976-July 1977 (Box 280)
  - Sco-Tr, July 1976-July 1977 (Box 281)
  - Ts-Z, July 1976-July 1977 (Box 282)
  - A-Ch, July 1977-July 1978 (Box 283)
  - Cl-E, July 1977-July 1978 (Box 284)
  - F-G, July 1977-July 1978 (Box 285)
  - H-J, July 1977-July 1978 (Box 286)
  - K-Ma, July 1977-July 1978 (Box 287)
  - Mc-N, July 1977-July 1978 (Box 288)
  - O-Ri, July 1977-July 1978 (Box 289)
  - Ro-So, July 1977-July 1978 (Box 290)
  - Sp-V, July 1977-July 1978 (Box 291)
  - W-Z, July 1977-July 1978 (Box 292)
  - A-B, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 293)
  - C-D, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 294)
  - E-G, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 295)
  - H-J, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 296)
  - K-L, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 297)
  - M, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 298)
  - N-Ri, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 299)
  - Ro-Stephen, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 300)
  - Stephenson-V, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 301)
  - W-Z, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 302)
  - A-B, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 303)
  - C-D, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 304)
  - E-G, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 305)
  - H-K, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 306)
  - L-M, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 307)
  - N-R, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 308)
  - S, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 309)
  - T-Z, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 310)
  - A-B, July 1980-June 1981 (Box 311)
  - C-De, July 1980-June 1981 (Box 312)
  - Di-F, July 1980-June 1981 (Box 313)
  - G-Hi, July 1980-June 1981 (Box 314)
  - Ho-Le, July 1980-June 1981 (Box 315)
  - M, July 1980-June 1981 (Box 316)
  - N-R, July 1980-June 1981 (Box 317)
  - S-T, July 1980-June 1981 (Box 318)
  - U-Z, July 1980-June 1981 (Box 319)
  - A-B, July 1981-June 1982 (Box 320)
  - C-D, July 1981-June 1982 (Box 321)
  - E-Ha, July 1981-June 1982 (Box 322)
  - He-Le, July 1981-June 1982 (Box 323)
  - Li-P, July 1981-June 1982 (Box 324)
  - Q-Sn, July 1981-June 1982 (Box 325)
  - Su-Z, July 1981-June 1982 (Box 326)
  - A-B, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 327)
  - C-E, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 328)
  - F-H, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 329)
  - I-L, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 330)
  - M-Pe, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 331)
  - Ph-Sh, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 332)
  - So-Wl, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 333)
  - Wo-Z, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 334)
  - A-B, July 1983-June 1984 (Box 335)
  - C-D, July 1983-June 1984 (Box 336)
  - E-Ho, July 1983-June 1984 (Box 337)
  - Hu-Marx, July 1983-June 1984 (Box 338)
  - Mas-Pa, July 1983-June 1984 (Box 339)
  - Pe-Si, July 1983-June 1984 (Box 340)
  - Sk-Z, July 1983-June 1984 (Box 341)
  - A-Ca, July 1984-June 1985 (Box 342)
  - Ce-E, July 1984-June 1985 (Box 343)
  - F-H, July 1984-June 1985 (Box 344)
  - I-M, July 1984-June 1985 (Box 345)
  - Me-Rh, July 1984-June 1985 (Box 346)
  - Ri-Ste, July 1984-June 1985 (Box 347)
  - Sti-Z, July 1984-June 1985 (Box 348)
- Deceased From July 1985 Onward
  For alumni deceased during this period box numbers can be retrieved upon request.